//creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answer
let questions=[
  {
    numb:1,
    question:"What is the flashes real name?",
    answer:"Barry Allen",
    options:[
      "Hendry allen",
      "Bart Allen",
      "Barry Allen",
      "Tom Allen"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:2,
    question:"How many Oscas Does Nolan Have?",
    answer:"192",
    options:[
      "192",
      "234",
      "222",
      "100"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:3,
    question:"What is the number 1 highest grossing movie?",
    answer:"Avatar",
    options:[
      "Titanic",
      "Avengers end game",
      "Spiderman into the spiderverse",
      "Avatar"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb:4,
    question:"What is the longest movie ever?",
    answer:"The Cure for Insomnia",
    options:[
      "Gone with the wind",
      "The Cure for Insomnia",
      "Avatar",
      "Titanic"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:5,
    question:"Who is the real creator of Spider-man?",
    answer:"Stan Lee",
    options:[
      "Jack Kirby",
      "Larry Lieber",
      "Stan Lee",
      "Mike Zeck"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:6,
    question:"In The Matrix, what color pill does Neo take?",
    answer:"Red",
    options:[
      "Red",
      "Blue",
      "Green",
      "Black"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:7,
    question:"What is the highest-grossing R-rated movie of all time?",
    answer:"Joker",
    options:[
      "The Matrix",
      "Joker",
      "Chain Saw",
      "Kill Bill"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:8,
    question:"Who wrote the screenplay for Rocky?",
    answer:"Sylvester Stallone",
    options:[
      "Sylvester Stallone",
      "Reservier Dogs",
      "Grace Kelly",
      "Alex Martin"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:9,
    question:"Who plays Ironman/Tony stark in Ironman?",
    answer:"Robert Downey Jr",
    options:[
      "Wills smith",
      "Robert Downey Jr",
      "Chris Evans",
      "Chris Hemsworth"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb:10,
    question:"Who is the creator of Tenet?",
    answer:"Christopher Nolan",
    options:[
      "Steven Spielberg",
      "Christopher Nolan",
      "Alfred Hitchcock",
      "Martin Scorsese"
    ]
  }
];